{
  "type": "flashcards",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "去" ,
      "answer": "Qù | to go"
    },
    {
      "question": "游泳",
      "answer": "Yóuyǒng | to swim"
    },
    {
      "question": "昨天" ,
      "answer": "Zuótiān | yesterday"
    },
    {
      "question": "京剧",
      "answer": "Jīngjù | Beijing opera"
    },
    {
      "question": "怎么样",
      "answer": "Zěnme yàng | how is ..."
    },
    {
      "question": "有意思",
      "answer": "Yǒuyìsi | interesting"
    },
    {
      "question": "今天",
      "answer": "Jīntiān | today"
    },
    {
      "question": "天",
      "answer": "tiān | day"
    },
    {
      "question": "天气",
      "answer": "Tiānqì | weather"
    },
    {
      "question": "太",
      "answer": "Tài | too, extremely"
    },
    {
      "question": "什么",
      "answer": "Shénme | what"
    },
    {
      "question": "时候",
      "answer": "Shíhòu | time, moment"
    },
    {
      "question": "现在",
      "answer": "Xiànzài | now"
    }
  ]
}
